Guide to the Gay Cable Network Archives, 1982-2001 MSS.231
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Gay USA
  - 1997 Vol. XV
    - Gay USA, Vol. XV, Episode No. 49 [Air date: 12/11/1997], December 1997; ID: 231.0275 (Box 18, Media ID: 231.0275)
      6. Clip of film "Six Ladies Laughing".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XV, Episode No. 50 [Air date: 12/19/1997], December 1997; ID: 231.0276 (Box 18, Media ID: 231.0276)
      2. Interview: Ed Sederbaum, activist and candidate for NYS Senate, discusses his running for office.
      COMMERCIAL: Cable Positive, "The fight continues."
      4. Footage from NY1 of gay veterans speaking at a NYC Council hearing regarding the military recruitment station in Times Square. Includes NY1 interview with Peter Vallone, City Council Speaker, regarding Tom Duane's efforts regarding the recruitment station.
      7. Interview: Christine Quinn, Executive Director of the Gay and Lesbian Anti-Violence Project, discusses a series of pick-up crimes in Miami committed by Damian Escobar and Roberto Ortiz, who may be headed to NY.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XV, Episode No. 51 [Air date: 12/25/1997], December 1997; ID: 231.0277 (Box 18, Media ID: 231.0277)
    - [Cassette]--Gay USA Year in Review Great Opening [Container]--Gay USA Demo 97, 1997; ID: 231.0575 (Box 36, Media ID: 231.0575)
  - 1998 Vol. XVI
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 1 [Air date: 1/7/1998], January 1998; ID: 231.0051 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0051)
      2. Interview: Charles Kaiser, author, discusses his book "The Gay Metropolis 1940-1996"
      4. Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund presents "The Lambda Update", with Beatrice Dohrn, Director, and Evan Wolfson, Senior Staff Attorney.
      6. Promo for "In the Life"
      7. Andrew Taines interviews Mike Willis, director, and Andrew Elvis Miller, actor, regarding their play "Fixing Frank".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 2 [Air date: 1/15/1998], January 1998; ID: 231.0052 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0052)
      2. Interview: Maura Bairley, Community Organizer with the Gay and Lesbian Anti-Violence Project, discusses the disappearance of Cosmetica, AKA Cosmo or Freddie Messina.
      4. Interview: Jonathan Lee, of the Maine SpeakOut Project, discusses the Maine anti-discrimination law and right-wing opposition.
      6. Interview: Mark Milano, of ACT UP New York, discusses recent HIV drug trials.
      7. Lou Maletta interviews Robert E. Penn, author, regarding his book "The Gay Men's Wellness Guide".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 3 [Air date: 1/22/1998], January 1998; ID: 231.0053 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0053)
      COMMERCIAL: Blue Ball "Come to Life" event in Philadelphia to benefit AIDS Information Network
      3. Interview: Ronald Johnson, of the Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC), discusses the name-based reporting of HIV-related information.
      4. Lou Maletta interviews Robert E. Penn, author, regarding his book "The Gay Men's Wellness Guide".
      6. Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund presents "The Lambda Update", with Kevin Cathcart, Executive Director, and Suzanne Goldberg, Staff Attorney.
      7. Clip from "Speak Out!" video by [Ellen Spiro].
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 4 [Air date: 1/28/1998], January 1998; ID: 231.0054 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0054)
      2. Interview: Michael Swirsky, of ACT UP New York, discusses the name-based reporting of HIV-related information.
      4. Lou Maletta interviews Kate Bornstein, author, regarding her book "My Gender Workbook"
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Doug Witkins, writer and director, regarding his film "No Ordinary Love". Includes film footage.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 5 [Air date: 2/5/1998], February 1998; ID: 231.0055 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0055)
      2. Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund presents "The Lambda Update", with Beatrice Dohrn, Legal Director, and David Buckel, Staff Attorney.
      3. AIDS News. Includes footage of ACT UP demonstration against Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC).
      4. Entertainment, includes promo for "Crossings", a lesbian romantic comedy play by Barbara Kahn.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 6 [Air date: 2/12/1998], February 1998; ID: 231.0056 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0056)
      2. Interview: Matt Foreman, Executive Director of Empire State Pride Agenda, discusses political issues affecting the LGBT community.
      5. Lou Maletta interviews Perry Brass, author, regarding his books "The Harvest" and "The Lover of My Soul".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 7 [Air date: 2/19/1998], February 1998; ID: 231.0057 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0057)
      3. Fox News footage of "Surgeon General Swearing In Ceremony" for David Satcher.
      4. Andrew Taines interviews Jeffrey Solomon, playwright and actor, regarding his play "Mother/Son". Includes Solomon performing the part of Mother.
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Christopher Bradley, actor, regarding the film "Leather Jacket Love Story," in which Bradley stars. Includes film footage.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 8 [Air date: 2/26/1998], February 1998; ID: 231.0058 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0058)
      1. Paul Schindler and Ann Northrop discuss recent general events that relate to the LGBT community.
      2. Interview: Fran DeBenedictis, Executive Director of the Gay Officers Action League (GOAL), and Susan O'Brien, member of the Irish Lesbian and Gay Organization (ILGO), discuss St. Patrick's Day events.
      5. Clip from Tracey Ullman's show ["Tracey Takes On…"]. Includes introduction by Andy Humm.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 9 [Air date: 3/5/1998], March 1998; ID: 231.0059 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0059)
      2. Interview: James Dale, former Eagle Scout, and David Buckel, Staff Attorney at Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, discuss Dale's case discrimination case against the Boy Scouts of America.
      4. Lou Maletta interviews Dean LaBate, Executive Director of Callen – Lorde Community Health Center, regarding the organization's new facility. Includes Maletta touring the facility.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 10 [Air date: 3/12/1998], March 1998; ID: 231.0060 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0060)
      2. Footage of Betty DeGeneres, mother of Ellen DeGeneres, on the Leeza talk show. Includes Human Rights Campaign PSA featuring Betty DeGeneres.
      COMMERCIAL: H.E.L.P./Project Samaritan, Inc.
      5. Nora Burns discusses recent nightlife and entertainment-related events that relate to the LGBT community.
      6. Lou Maletta interviews a group of performers, regarding their Hebrew-based program "Words of His Own". Includes performance footage.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 11 [Air date: 3/19/1998], March 1998; ID: 231.0061 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0061)
      2. Footage of Irish Lesbian and Gay Organization (ILGO) St. Patrick's Day March Protest.
      6. Interview: Andrew Taines, theatre critic, discusses recent entertainment-related events.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 12 [Air date: 3/26/1998], March 1998; ID: 231.0062 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0062)
      4. Nora Burns discusses recent nightlife and entertainment-related events that relate to the LGBT community.
      5. Lou Maletta interviews Delmas Howe, artist, regarding his exhibit "Stations: A Gay Passion" at the Leslie-Lohman Gay Art Foundation.
      6. Stonewall Veterans Association event promotion
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 13 [Air date: 4/2/1998], April 1998; ID: 231.0063 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0063)
      COMMERCIAL: American Social Health Association, PSA for genital warts
      3. Interview: Nancy Manahan, author, discusses her book "On My Honor".
      5. Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund presents "The Lambda Update", with Kevin Cathcart, Executive Director, and Heather Sawyer, Staff Attorney, Midwest Region.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 15 [Air date: 4/9/1998], April 1998; ID: 231.0576 (Box 36, Media ID: 231.0576)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 16 [Air date: 4/16/1998], April 1998; ID: 231.0064 (Box 4, Media ID: 231.0064)
      2. Interview: Steve Cozza, founder of Scouting for All, and Sergeant Edgar Rodriguez, President of the Gay Officers Action League (GOAL), discuss Scouting For All, an organization created by Cozza in response to discrimination from the Boy Scouts of America, as well as the GOAL annual dinner in which Cozza will be honored.
      6. Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund presents "The Lambda Update", with Kevin Cathcart, Executive Director, and Heather Sawyer, Staff Attorney, Midwest Region.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 17 [Air date: 4/23/1998], April 1998; ID: 231.0065 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0065)
      COMMERCIAL: Out on the Edge Together Festival '98
      2. Interview: Candido Gonzalez and Andy Stern, of the Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC), discuss governmental funding and access issues regarding people with HIV.
      4. Footage of Donna Shalala discussing vaccinations on The Rosie O'Donnell Show.
      5. Interview: Gary Mallon, Executive Director of Green Chimneys, discusses LGBT youth homelessness.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 18 [Air Date: 4/30/1998], April 1998; ID: 231.0066 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0066)
      2. Footage of Reggie White on ABC's 20/20 regarding his controversial comments on homosexuality.
      4. Entertainment, includes special celebration for Ann Northrop's 50th birthday.
      5. Andrew Taines interviews Scott Dobbins, Co-Executive Producer of the Out on the Edge Together Festival, regarding the festival.
      6. Interview: Marvin Schwam, of Gay Entertainment Television (GET), discusses GET's going public.
      7. Nora Burns discusses recent nightlife and entertainment-related events that relate to the LGBT community.
      8. Interview: Terry Kaelber, Executive Director of Senior Action in a Gay Environment (SAGE), and Madelin Alk, Vice President of SAGE, discuss the first national conference on aging in the LGBT community.
      9. Footage of Walter Schubert, CEO of the Gay Financial Network (GFN), speaking at the Launch Party for GFN.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 19 [Air date: 5/7/1998], May 1998; ID: 231.0067 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0067)
      2. Interview: Carren Strock, author, discusses her book "Married Women Who Love Women".
      4. Lou Maletta interviews Brian Sloan, director, regarding his film "I Think I Do". Includes film footage.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 20 [Air date: 5/14/1998], May 1998; ID: 231.0068 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0068)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 21 [Air date: 5/21/1998], May 1998; ID: 231.0577 (Box 37, Media ID: 231.0577)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 22 [Air date: 5/28/1998], May 1998; ID: 231.0069 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0069)
      2. Footage from NY1 of Cardinal John Joseph O'Connor denouncing proposed domestic partner benefits legislation.
      3. Interview: Steve Ault and Leslie Cagan, activists, discuss the Millennium March on Washington.
      COMMERCIAL: National AIDS Hotline, "Protect your kids from AIDS. Talk with them about sex".
      COMMERCIAL: National AIDS Hotline, "Isn't it time you talked with your kids?" Features Kerry Carson, activist.
      5. Interview: Dennis Beauchemin, victim of bias crime, discusses his assault.
      COMMERCIAL: National AIDS Hotline, "Carry the torch. Talk about AIDS."
      COMMERCIAL: National AIDS Hotline, "Make the effort. Talk about sex. Protect your kids from AIDS".
      7. Footage from the 20th Annual International Mr. Leather contest.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 23 [Air date: 6/4/1998], June 1998; ID: 231.0070 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0070)
      COMMERCIAL: Sierra Club
      3. Lou Maletta interviews Guy Kettelhack, author, regarding his book "Easing the Ache"
      5. Footage of Earvin 'Magic' Johnson, basketball player, on The Rosie O'Donnell Show discussing his new talk show.
      6. Nora Burns discusses recent nightlife and entertainment-related events that relate to the LGBT community.
      7. Footage of Kate Clinton, comedian, on The Rosie O'Donnell Show discussing her personal life.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 24 [Air date: 6/11/1998], June 1998; ID: 231.0578 (Box 37, Media ID: 231.0578)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 25 [Air date: 6/18/1998], June 1998; ID: 231.0071 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0071)
      3. Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund presents "The Lambda Update", with Kevin Cathcart, Executive Director, and John Scarborough, Staff Attorney, Southern Regional Office.
      5. Andrew Taines discusses entertainment-related events.
      7. Interview: Paul Harris, playwright, and Patrick [Lloyd], director, discuss their play "To Have and To Hold".
      8. Lou Maletta interviews John Weis, chairman of Gay-Male-S/M Activists (GMSMA), regarding the Folsom Street East block party.
      9. Clip from "In the Life" show, "American as Apple Pie" episode
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 26 [Air date: 6/25/1998], June 1998; ID: 231.0072 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0072)
      3. Footage of Peter Vallone, Speaker of NYC Council; Alan Hevesi, NYC Comptroller; Deborah Glick, NYS Assembly member; and Kate Clinton, comedian, at the 15th Annual Center Garden Party
      4. Footage of Pride Rally, including speech by Margarita Lopez, NYC Council Member.
      5. Footage of the Gay Officers Action League's "Heritage of Courage Celebration"
      6. Footage of Folsom Street East II
      7. Footage of the Mr. LURE Contest
      8. Interview with Christopher Lynn, NYC politician.
      9. Entertainment, includes Nora Burns discussing recent nightlife and entertainment-related events that relate to the LGBT community.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 27 [Air date: 7/2/1998], July 1998; ID: 231.0073 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0073)
      2. Footage from CSPAN regarding the "Legal Age of Homosexual Consent" in the United Kingdom.
      3. Footage of Pride Month event in which Mark Green, [politician], honors activists at City Hall. Includes footage of Harry Bartel and Brian Landeche, owners of Splash bar; Craig Lucas, playwright; and Betty Santoro, member of Lesbian Feminist Liberation.
      4. Footage of activists protesting the mayor's participation in the Lesbian and Gay Pride March.
      6. Interview: James LaRocca, candidate for the Democratic primary for Governor of New York, discusses his political platform with respect to LGBT issues.
      7. Footage of Tom of Finland at the Manhunt Party.
      8. Nora Burns discusses recent nightlife and entertainment-related events that relate to the LGBT community.
      9. Entertainment
      10. Footage of the 1998 Gay and Lesbian Pride Parade. Includes footage of NYC politicians Margarita Lopez, Peter Vallone, Rudy Giuliani, Alan Hevesi, and Mark Green.
      11. Footage of Pier Dance.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 28 [Air date: 7/9/1998], July 1998; ID: 231.0074 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0074)
      1. Andy Humm and Frank Jump discuss recent general events that relate to the LGBT community.
      2. Interview: James LaRocca, candidate for the Democratic primary for Governor of New York, discusses his political platform with respect to LGBT issues.
      4. Interview: Dennis Hensley, author, discusses his book "Misadventures in the (213)".
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Louise Rafkin, author, regarding her book "Other People's Dirt: A Housecleaner's Curious Adventures".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 29 [Air date: 7/16/1998], July 1998; ID: 231.0075 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0075)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 30 [Air date: 7/23/1998], July 1998; ID: 231.0076 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0076)
      Program content: [Callen-Lorde]
      2. Interview: Paula Ettelbrick, veteran activist, discusses the upcoming national event Equality Begins at Home.
      4. Callen - Lorde Community Health Center Update.
      5. Nora Burns interviews Jeffrey, Jeff, and Lance, members of the New York Express gay basketball team.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 31 [Air date: 7/30/1998], July 1998; ID: 231.0077 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0077)
      2. Interview: Laura Moore, Gay Games Figure Skater, discusses the upcoming fifth Gay Games in Amsterdam.
      4. Interview: Michael Shernoff, editor, discusses his book "Gay Widowers: Life After the Death of a Partner".
      5. Interview: Stanley Bojarski and Michael West, cast members, discuss the musical "Howard Crabtree's When Pigs Fly". Includes performance footage.
      COMMERCIAL: Cable Positive, PSA for AIDS information
      8. Additional footage of "Howard Crabtree's When Pigs Fly".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 32 [Air date: 8/6/1998], August 1998; ID: 231.0078 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0078)
      2. Footage from CSPAN of Nancy Pelosi, Democratic Representative for the House of Representatives, regarding "Domestic Partners and Employees Benefits" legislation.
      3. Footage from NY1 of US Senate press conference. Includes footage of politicians Betsy McCaughey Ross, Margarita Lopez, James Larocca, Geraldine Ferraro, and Alan Hevesi, and activist Andy Humm.
      4. Footage from News at Ten of the Gay Games at Amsterdam.
      6. Interview: Joe Calarco, production adapter and director, discusses his all-male play "Shakespeare's R & J". Includes performance footage.
      7. Callen - Lorde Community Health Center Update.
      8. Entertainment
      9. Interview: Arthur Hanket, playwright and actor, discusses his solo play "Saint Genet: Language of the Wall". Includes performance footage.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 33 [Air date: 8/13/1998], August 1998; ID: 231.0079 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0079)
      1. Andy Humm and Barbara Raab discuss recent general events that relate to the LGBT community.
      2. Interview: Mitchell Anderson, actor, discusses "Visiting Mr. Green", a play in which he stars.
      5. Andrew Taines interviews Jeff Krell, author, and Craig Dawson, actor, regarding Krell's comic strip "Jayson" and its stage production.
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Alvino Najar, artist and sculptor, regarding his artwork and personal life.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 34 [Air date: 8/20/1998], August 1998; ID: 231.0080 (Box 5, Media ID: 231.0080)
      3. Footage of Andy Humm interviewing Clyde Rabideau, Mayor of Plattsburgh, NY, and Candidate for Lieutenant Governor of NY State, regarding his political platform.
      5. Lou Maletta interviews Ren Volpe, author, regarding her book "The Lady Mechanic's Total Car Care for the Clueless: A Manual for Car Owners".
      6. Footage of the 16th Annual GMHC (Gay Men's Health Crisis) Morning Party on Fire Island. Includes footage of Lou Maletta interviewing partygoers.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 36 [Air date: 9/3/1998], September 1998; ID: 231.0082 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0082)
      3. Lou Maletta interviews Mike Parker, artist, regarding his Disney and entertainment-inspired paintings.
      5. Footage of Ryan Phillippe as gay teenager Billy on the soap opera "One Life to Live".
      6. Footage of "The Queen's Cantonese Conversational Course" video from the Leslie-Lohman Gay Art Foundation's Homoerotic Video Trash II. Introduced by Lou Maletta.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 37 [Air date: 9/10/1998], September 1998; ID: 231.0083 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0083)
      2. Interview: Tom Duane, NYC Council Member, discusses recent crimes against the LGBT community.
      5. Footage of Wigstock '98. Includes footage of Lou Maletta interviewing attendees.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 38 [Air date: 9/17/1998], September 1998; ID: 231.0084 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0084)
      1. Interview: Matt Foreman, Executive Director of the Empire State Pride Agenda, discusses the recent election results and their effects on the LGBT community.
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Arch Brown, playwright, regarding his play "Freeze!". Includes performance footage.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 39 [Air date: 9/24/1998], September 1998; ID: 231.0085 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0085)
      2. Interview: Sergeant Edgar Rodriguez, President of the Gay Officers Action League (GOAL), discusses police department events and recent crimes against the LGBT community.
      5. Lou Maletta interviews Miss Naomi, author, regarding her book "Forbidden Art: The World of Erotica". COMMERCIAL: Lesbian and Gay Public Awareness Project, tells the story of Bobby Griffith
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 40 [Air date: 10/1/1998], October 1998; ID: 231.0086 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0086)
      4. Lou Maletta interviews Barry Wyatt, actor, regarding his personal life and his acting role in the film "Skin & Bone". Includes film footage.
      COMMERCIAL: The New Ramrod Showplace
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 41 [Air date: 10/1/1998], October 1998; ID: 231.0087 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0087)
      1. Footage of Virginia Apuzzo, [activist], and Al Gore, US Vice President, speaking at the Empire State Pride Agenda Awards Dinner. Includes footage of Andy Humm interviewing attendees.
      5. Interview: Dan Savage, Sex Advice Columnist, discusses his book "Savage Love".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 42 [Air date: 10/15/1998], October 1998; ID: 231.0579 (Box 37, Media ID: 231.0579)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 42 [Air date: 10/15/1998] [Empty], October 1998; ID: 231.0489 (Box 31, Media ID: 231.0489)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 43 [Air date: 10/22/1998], October 1998; ID: 231.0088 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0088)
      2. Interview: Suzy Lee Korn, organizer of New York protest, discusses the recent rally to protest the killing of Matthew Shepard.
      4. Interview: Katherine Acey, Executive Director of the ASTREA National Lesbian Action Foundation, discusses the organization's turning 20 years old.
      5. Interview: [Sean] discusses the play "Corpus Christi" by Terrence McNally.
      6. Lou Maletta interviews Roland Tec, writer and director, and Paul [Outlaw], actor, regarding Tec's film "All the Rage". Includes film footage.
      7. Footage of the Peace March for Matthew Shepard. Includes footage of Lou Maletta and Andy Humm at the event.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 44 [Air date: 10/29/1998], October 1998; ID: 231.0089 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0089)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 45 [Air date: 11/5/1998], November 1998; ID: 231.0090 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0090)
      2. Interview: Tim Sweeney, Deputy Director of the Empire State Pride Agenda, discusses political issues that affect the LGBT community.
      5. Interview: Jay Corcoran, director, discusses his film "Undetectable" following three men and three women taking protease [inhibitors] to combat HIV. Includes film footage.
      6. Peter Sparrow interviews Ron Athey, performance artist, regarding the documentary "Hallelujah! Ron Athey: A Story of Deliverance". Includes film trailer.
      7. Additional footage of Jay Corcoran's film "Undetectable".
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 46 [Air date: 11/12/1998], November 1998; ID: 231.0091 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0091)
      2. Footage of Andy Humm for Marriage Equality at Same Sex Marriage Rally. Includes footage of Evan Wolfson, of Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund; Dick Gottfried, of the NYS Assembly; Kathryn Freed, of the NYC Council; Tim Sweeney, of the Empire State Pride Agenda; Patty Penalosa, of Marriage Equality; Kevin McGruder, Gay Men of African Descent, Rabbi Sharon Kleinbaum, of the [Lesbian and Gay] Synagogue; John Magisano, of the Metropolitan Community Church; and Joe DeFilippis, [activist].
      5. Interview: Deian McBryde, entertainer, regarding his personal life and artistic work. Includes McBryde performing "I'll Be True to You" from his CD "Mollyboy".
      6. Interview: Paul Wirhun, artist, discusses his artistic egg designs.
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 47 [Air date: 11/19/1998], November 1998; ID: 231.0092 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0092)
    - Gay USA, Vol. XVI, Episode No. 48 [Air date: 11/26/1998], November 1998; ID: 231.0093 (Box 6, Media ID: 231.0093)